(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
ホロライブファンクラブ！
Hololive Fan Club!
一条莉々華だよ！
It's Ichijou Lirika!
I'm Mori Calliope.
ホロライブファンクラブ、始まりました！
Hololive Fan Club has begun!
ここだけのオリジナルグッズや、チケット先行抽選。
Exclusive original goods and early ticket lottery.
他にも楽しいコンテンツがいっぱい！
And many other fun contents!
Campaigns too? That sounds really fun. I'm curious.
さあみんな、ホロライブファンクラブで一緒に楽しもう！
Now everyone, let's enjoy Hololive Fan Club together!
Join us now!
ゆくホロくるホロ2023! 年末年始デートボイス
Yuku Holo Kuru Holo 2023! Year-End/New Year Date Voice
ここは露天風呂が有名だって言うから、
I heard the open-air bath here is famous,
ずっと気になってたんだよね〜！
so I've been curious about it for a long time!
……ね、キミも一緒に行かない？
...Hey, won't you come with me?
ええっ！？一緒に、入るって意味じゃないよ！？
Eh!? I don't mean entering *together*!?
おーそーじ！モココ、大掃除やってみたいんだよね！
Big clean-up! Mococo wants to try doing a big clean-up!
もちろんキミも一緒にやるんだよ！？
Of course, you're doing it with me!?
じゃあさっそく大掃除、開始だ〜！
Well then, let's start the big clean-up!
え〜？服のすきまがどうしたって〜？
Eh~? What about the gap in my clothes~?
僕が掃除している間に、キミはいったいどこを見てたのかな〜？
I wonder where you were looking while I was cleaning~?
お〜！ここが夢にまで見た日本の温泉街〜♪
Oh~! This is the Japanese hot spring town I've dreamed of~♪
ん？もしかして……
Hm? Could it be...
私と一緒に入りたいなとか、思ってる？
...you're thinking you want to get in with me?
……いいよ、一緒に入ろっか……？
...Okay, shall we get in together...?
って、やばいやばい！みんな、そろそろカウントダウン始まるよ！
Wait, oh no! Everyone, the countdown is about to start!
5!
4!
3!
2!
1!
0!
ハッピーニューイヤー！
Happy New Year!
あけましておめでとうございます！今年もよろしくお願いします！
Happy New Year! I look forward to working with you this year too!
えへへ……なんかあらためてかしこまると、はずかしくて照れちゃうね♪
Ehehe... getting formal like this is a bit embarrassing and makes me blush♪
ダイヤモンド富士っていうんだっけ？
Is it called Diamond Fuji?
ほらほら！だんだん富士山の輪郭が見えてきたよ！
Look look! The outline of Mt. Fuji is gradually becoming visible!
なんだかもう、この景色だけで感動するよ〜！
Somehow, I'm already moved just by this scenery~!
突然ですが、おせちを作りまーす！
It's sudden, but I'm going to make Osechi!
つまみ食いしちゃだめだよ？
No snacking, okay?
もしつまみ食いしちゃったら……
If you sneak a bite...
……ガブってしちゃうからねっ！？
...I'll take a big chomp!
おめでとー！おめでとー！
Congrats! Congrats!
キミとぎゅーしながらお祝い♪
Celebrating while hugging you♪
キミをぎゅーできるのはモココだけなんだから！
Because only Mococo can hug you!
ほらほらキミも、モココのこともぎゅーっとして！
C'mon, you hug Mococo too!
せーの！今年もよろしくお願いします！
One, two! We look forward to working with you this year too!
再販！ゆくホロ2023! くるホロ2024! 2タイトル好評販売中!
年末年始デートボイス
Resale! Yuku-Holo 2023! Kuru-Holo 2024! 2 titles now on sale!
Year-end/New Year's Date Voice
ホロ新春ゲーム祭 2026
Hololive New Year Game Festival 2026
夢の途中の
In the middle of a dream
一瞬一瞬を、
Each and every moment,
一緒に大切に。
Cherish them together.
過去最大規模の
On the largest scale ever
「そらぱ」がいま始まる。
'Sorapa' begins now.
ときのそら New Year's Party 2026 「Dreamin' in Motion」
2026.1.10 sat 東京国際フォーラム ホールA
Tokino Sora New Year's Party 2026 'Dreamin' in Motion'
2026.1.10 Sat Tokyo International Forum Hall A
hololive 3rd Generation
次に向かう舞台は
The next stage they face...
大作戦？
A big operation?
hololive 3rd Generation Live
#きゅるるん大作戦
#Kyururun Large Operation
最強アイドルに推すしかないでしょー
You've got to support the ultimate idols, right?
「好き」と「かわいい」を詰め込んで
Packed with "love" and "cute,"
あなたと作る大作戦！
a big operation created with you!
いっぱいのこれまでと
Everything so far,
ときめくような一瞬を！
and a heart-pounding moment!
ちなみに作戦の内容は
By the way, the details of the operation...
とにかくかわいい
are just "cute."
かわいいに満たされろ！
Be filled with cuteness!
作戦進行中！
Operation in progress!
ホロ新春 3期生24時間配信
1月2日(金) 20:00～
Hololive New Year 3rd Gen 24-hour Stream
Jan 2nd (Fri) 20:00-
hololive DEV_IS 正月衣装お披露目リレー
hololive DEV_IS New Year Outfit Reveal Relay
音乃瀬奏
Otonose Kanade
一条莉々華
Ichijou Ririka
儒烏風亭らでん
Juufuutei Raden
轟はじめ
Todoroki Hajime
響咲リオナ
Isaki Riona
虎金妃笑虎
Koganebi Niko
水宮枢
Mizumiya Su
輪堂千速
Rindo Chihaya
綺羅々ヴィヴィ
Kikirara Vivi
FLOW GLOW New Voice Pack Coming Soon
hololive production COUNTDOWN LIVE 2025▷2026
まもなく配信開始します
Stream starting soon
hololive production
hololive
COUNTDOWN LIVE
2025 ▷ 2026
1st STAGE
FG ROADSTER
作詞：ポチュムキン
作曲：ポチュムキン / LUNA / Joe Ogawa / Foux
編曲：Foux
FG ROADSTER
Lyrics: Potumukin
Music: Potumukin / LUNA / Joe Ogawa / Foux
Arrangement: Foux
This is FLOW GLOW in COUNTDOWN LIVE!
来年もよろしく！
Looking forward to next year too!
Let's go!
搭載V8エンジン
Equipped with a V8 engine
第7感持ってる現時
Currently possessing the seventh sense
ロックするこの世界と全人類
Locking down this world and all humanity
この5人でゲームは前進
With these five, the game moves forward
鳴る四輪ハッシャセヨ
Firing up the four wheels
皆さんサンキューサランヘヨ
Thank you everyone, Saranghaeyo
あつらえ2体のターンテーブル
Two custom-made turntables
ホロ一番カッコいいブランドゼロ
Holo's coolest brand, Zero
Ay リスク超えて挑戦
Ay, challenging beyond the risk
チャンスもセットだ当然
Opportunities come as a set, naturally
上り上げる頂点
Climbing to the peak
座布団積んでいけ勝点
Stack up cushions and victory points
乗り込めFGロードスター
Hop into the FG Roadster
特殊部隊集合能力者
Special forces gathering, those with powers
この歴史に残る独走下
In this historic solo run
ぶっちぎりでおきざりこの勝者
Pulling far ahead and leaving others behind, the winner
今高速でぶち抜いて
Piercing through at high speed now
いく大気圏
Going to the atmosphere
エンジンからジェットのほうへ
From engine to jet
入れている怪気炎
Emitting high spirits
眼下に広がる大地越えていく
Crossing the earth spread out below
階級制
The class system
バックミラーにピックブルーが映ってる
Pink blue reflected in the rearview mirror
I BELIEVE I FIRE
ぶち開けたいから飛んでくうちら世代
Our generation flies because we want to break through
この燃料朽ち果てない
This fuel will never decay
銀河寿司食べたい
Want to eat galaxy sushi
見えてるでっかいビジョン
I see a big vision
燃えてるメンバー一途
The members are burning with single-mindedness
ただいま現在進行形
Right now, we're in the present progressive
超えてく世界規模
Exceeding the global scale
叶うハズさモンスター
It should come true, monster
心臓がモンスター
The heart is a monster
エイリアン在住のターミナル
A terminal where aliens live
FG PARTY HARD
光るテスラローター
Shining Tesla rotor
唸るブースター
Roaring booster
目覚めていく本能を
Awakening instincts
青い炎を
Blue flames
VIP Let's go out!
研ぎ澄ませ風 ゼロから
Sharpen the wind, from zero
空まで 囚われ
To the sky, captive
走るFGロードスター
The FG Roadster runs
唸るブースター
Roaring booster
FLOW GLOW the space to be
今チェイスミー
Chase me now
研ぎ澄ませ風 ゼロから
Sharpen the wind, from zero
空まで 囚われ
To the sky, captive
走るFGロードスター
The FG Roadster runs
泡月スーパーカー
Awatsuki Supercar
ハンドルさばきも半端ねぇ
Steering is no joke
キャッシュもハッシュも
Both cash and hash
16重奏中ばっか
Always in 16-part harmony
Ay 牙を剥き出して ギリギリ
Ay, baring fangs, just barely
モーター全開 じりびき
Motor at full throttle, jiribiki
そらから 導き
Guidance from the sky
お肌が ピチピチ
Skin is moist and firm
タイヤ焦がしてドーナツ化
Scorching tires, making donuts
弾け飛んでくドラム缶
Drum cans bursting and flying
顧客満足度高くて
Customer satisfaction is high
ぶち上がってるお客さん
Customers getting hyped up
ゼロから最高到達点
From zero to the highest point
溜めてる太陽光発電
Storing solar power
探索するこの小惑星
Exploring this asteroid
超覚醒たちにニューボーナスデー
A new bonus day for the super-awakened
一直線伸びてる道のバイブレーション
Vibration of the road stretching in a straight line
エンジンの鼓動
Engine heartbeat
速度増し上がってる鼓動
Increasing speed, rising heartbeat
限界重力凌駕し上昇
Surpassing gravity limit and rising
開拓しまくってくフロンティア
Plowing through the frontier
旅立つのロードスター オンリーワン
The Roadster departs, only one
アクセル踏み込んでく土壇場
Stepping on the gas at the critical moment
飛んでく日本中 さぁ
Flying all over Japan, now
1億馬力の重低音
100 million horsepower deep bass
火星の果てまで休憩所
Rest areas all the way to the end of Mars
並んで走行 UFO
UFOs driving alongside
降り立つ宇宙ステーション
Landing on a space station
物語継承 Ay
Inheriting the story, Ay
まるで旧約聖書 Ay
Just like the Old Testament, Ay
この先何世紀も成長
Growing for centuries to come
生き延びて結果出していこう
Let's survive and produce results
叶うハズさモンスター
It should come true, monster
心臓がモンスター
The heart is a monster
エイリアン在住のターミナル
A terminal where aliens live
FG PARTY HARD
光るテスラローター
Shining Tesla rotor
唸るブースター
Roaring booster
目覚めていく本能を
Awakening instincts
青い炎を
Blue flames
VIP Let's go out!
研ぎ澄ませ風 ゼロから
Sharpen the wind, from zero
空まで 囚われ
To the sky, captive
走るFGロードスター
The FG Roadster runs
唸るブースター
Roaring booster
FLOW GLOW
以上、私たちFLOW GLOWでしたー！
That's all from us, FLOW GLOW!
こっから先も楽しんでいこう！
Let's keep enjoying the rest of the show!
Tame the fire and bow before my justice
Final warning, you know my rage is limitless
On the advent of a new Genesis
I'm infamous, yeah, I get a little villainous
Look into my eyes, I'll take you up a level
The true face that you just can't hide
Clawing at the walls, I feel these sick temptations
What do I have to sacrifice?
Bound by chains, desiring to do it my way
This hurricane of a devastating force is coming
Out of the maze, feel my pulse is rising
And igniting fire, snap it out!
Walking the line on the edge of
Becoming what I never thought I'd be better
This state of gonna take them all out, RENEGADE!
Walking the line, fell so far
Into poison and seeing a new gotcha
Locked and I'm loaded, take them all out
RENEGADE, justice is just like that!
Don't care at all, I'll go deeper
'Till I can quit, never gonna stop 'cause I don't have a limit
My moral compass is out of focus
RENEGADE, make it a little wake up!
The light goes out! (Ha!)
The light goes out! (Oh!)
The light goes out! (Uh!)
The light goes out! (Ha!)
The light goes out!
I'm making it go down, make it make it
Your life switch, make it make it go down in the crash
RENEGADE, I'll make up
Make it go down, make it make it
Your life switch, make it make it go down in the crash
RENEGADE, I'll make up
Bound by a focus on the pretty one desiring
Never making a sound, ink on the needle, are you all ready?
Burning a mountain for all of us and in the ashes
Yeah, snap it out!
Walking the line on the edge of
Becoming what I never thought I'd be better
This state of gonna take them all out, RENEGADE!
Walking the line, fell so far
Into poison and seeing a new gotcha
Locked and I'm loaded, take them all out
RENEGADE, justice is just like that!
Don't care at all, I'll go deeper
'Till I can quit, never gonna stop 'cause I don't have a limit
My moral compass is out of focus
RENEGADE, make it a little wake up!
The light goes out! (Ha!)
The light goes out! (Yeah!)
The light goes out! (Ho!)
The light goes out! (Ha!)
Tame the fire and bow before my justice
Final warning, you know my rage is limitless
On the advent of a new Genesis
I'm infamous, yeah, I get a little villainous
The light goes out!
空覚えだもん人生ゲーム
Life game is just a rough memory
言い訳みたハートに従って
Following the heart that looks like an excuse
現実は半熟のフロートです
Reality is a soft-boiled float
取り憑かれるオーバチュア
Overture being possessed
世渡り上手なあのコはね
That girl who's good at navigating the world
二度とかぶった猫剥がせない
Can't peel off the mask she's wearing again
痛みを知ってしまったマジシャン
The magician who has come to know pain
手の内はまだ明かせない
I still can't reveal my hand
Yellow Yellow ゼロからループ
Yellow Yellow loop from zero
点滅するピリオド
Blinking period
Yellow Yellow 染まる赤い結晶
Yellow Yellow stained red crystal
Never life, can make it on time
ずっと追い続けてたいだけに見離されても
Even if I'm abandoned just because I want to keep chasing
No worry 私には私が付いてる
No worry, I have myself with me
宵が醒めるまで あと少しだけ
Just a little longer until the night wakes up
真実捉える残像 So step with the race
An afterimage capturing the truth, so step with the race
次の季節を越え Bloom me Bloom me
Beyond the next season, Bloom me Bloom me
どうかこの音を止めないで
Please don't stop this sound
Our time yellow yellow lollipop lollipop ずっとしたい子
Our time yellow yellow lollipop lollipop, the one who wants it forever
Our time yellow yellow lollipop lollipop Oh Oh Let's enjoy the moment
Looking into the mirror 絡まってる蜘蛛の糸
Looking into the mirror, entangled spider webs
It happens overtime 躍らされたままじゃ不満だ
It happens overtime, I'm not satisfied with being played
欲に従って時を編み上げて
Follow your desires and weave time together
Always be honest 永遠に変わらないもの
Always be honest, something that will never change
Yellow yellow 手を取り合えば そこに理由はいらない
Yellow yellow, if we hold hands, we don't need a reason
Yellow yellow 染まる赤い結晶 熱い衝動 Bad Bad
Yellow yellow, the red crystals are dyed, hot impulse Bad Bad
It's not a dream, just a test, 希望に目を閉じず
It's not a dream, just a test, without closing your eyes to hope
退屈すぎた運命や人生ごと受け入れ
Accept your boring fate and life as a whole
真摯に手探り 読めない 展開 掴んで
Sincere groping, grab the unreadable development
Run Run Jump 準備いいかい ぶち抜いて Go Out
Run Run Jump, are you ready? Punch through and Go Out
立ち抜ける 01 忘れて 執着地点 上へ Or Heaven
Breaking through 01, forget it, to the final point, upwards Or Heaven
No time to wait 今だけを信じて 最後のフィナーレまで共に進め
No time to wait, believe only in the now, move forward together until the final finale
宵が醒めるまで あと少しだけ
Just a little longer until the night wakes up
真実捉える残像 So step with the race
An afterimage capturing the truth, so step with the race
次の季節を越え Blue me Blue me
Beyond the next season, Bloom me Blue me
どうかこの音を止めないで
Please don't stop this sound
Our time yellow yellow lollipop lollipop ずっとしたい子
Our time yellow yellow lollipop lollipop, the one who wants it forever
Our time yellow yellow lollipop lollipop Oh Oh Let's enjoy the moment
またねー！
See ya!
楽しかったー！
That was fun!
ReGLOSSでした！バイバーイ！
We were ReGLOSS! Bye-bye!
Jump, open up your eyes, feel the music start to rise
Got to break the world and let me in
I knew I was meant to be, living life so fast and free
Try to keep your eyes on me, this is where my story all begins
Living in an epic legacy, ready for the brave to come and see
Give it away so easy, I can't get enough
Crossing borders, no limits, haven't you heard? I'm fearless
Ready, set, go, let's do this! Watch me, watch me, watch me...
...watch me be a diva, I'm gonna raise your fever, shaking up all the crowd
Making some noise when I'm not allowed, living my life out loud
I have awakened to wisdom beyond understanding
I keep on doubting in my anthem
Oh, don't blame me if I shine too bright
Oh, can't help it if I start a fire
Oh, pay attention to me, 'cause this is only the beginning
It's our Genesis!
Coming to wreak some havoc, how do you like this badness?
I'm embracing my madness, can you hear it?
Whispers bang around your window (Advent! Advent!)
Rumors reaching a crescendo (Advent! Advent!)
No humble beginning, I'm destined for great things
I'm sure you've heard of me by now, woah!
Midnight, diamonds in the dark side (Advent! Advent!)
Starlight, take me on a joyride (Advent! Advent!)
My crime is my passion, I'm mayhem in action
I know what day it is, this is our Genesis!
I enjoy the rage when I misbehave, take center stage
Let the funk commence, but you know I'm gonna get intense
There are loopholes I'm smoking, the rules can all be broken
I'm running on a rampage, the world is a blank page
I'm writing my story in flames and in glory
And they're gonna know me by name, some more!
Oh, this my promised land
Oh, the future's in my hands
Oh, they don't understand that I'm a star in the making, awaking, awaking!
Bow bow bow bow...
Tell me how you like me now.
Let's celebrate the new year!
Watch me, watch me, watch me.
Let your voice go up and show you how to lose control.
You've got to free your mind,
leave your base behind.
Be outrageous,
the chaos is contagious.
Come on, you know what time it is!
IT'S OUR GENESIS!
Time to open up your eyes,
feel the music start to rise,
got to shake the world and let me in.
I know what I was meant to be,
living life so fast and free,
try to keep your eyes on me,
this is our beginning!
IT'S OUR GENESIS!
Whispers banging down your window,
rumors reaching a crescendo.
No humble beginning,
a death-defying bracing,
I'm sure you've heard of me by now.
Tonight join me to the bright side,
day white take me on a joy ride.
My crime is my passion,
a mayhem in action.
I know what day it is,
THIS IS OUR GENESIS!
You know what time it is,
IT'S OUR GENESIS!
Tell me what time it is,
You know what time it is,
IT'S OUR GENESIS!
Tell me what time it is,
2nd STAGE
君に届けたい
I want to reach you
id:entity voices
そして明日への一歩踏み出した
And I've taken a step toward tomorrow
おはよう こんばんは
Good morning, good evening
この世界に叫んでみよう
Let's shout out to this world
本日のライブでは
In today's live performance,
どれの自分を見せるの
which side of myself will I show?
前からそう悩んで
I've been worrying like that for a while,
好きな自分になれない
unable to become the self I like
そしてある日誰かに言われた
And then one day, someone told me something
痛い言葉なんかに迷っていた
I was lost in some painful words
いつも作る笑顔失わないように
To make sure I don't lose the smile I always put on
これ以上は期待を
I decided I won't
裏切らないと決めた
disappoint expectations any further
溢れている
Amidst the
雑音の中
overflowing noise,
この声響けるか
can this voice resound?
心に宿る声を聞いてみよう
Let's try listening to the voice dwelling in our hearts
これはずっと見せたい自分だから
Because this is the self I've always wanted to show
集まった声たちが
The gathered voices
ひとつになる id:entity
become one, id:entity
君が過ぎてやっと
You passed by and finally
スポットライトに
under the spotlight,
立てるけれど
I can stand now but
少しだけ怖くなった
I've become a little bit scared
でもね一人じゃない
But you know, I'm not alone,
仲間たちがいるんだ
my friends are here
家族みたいな絆で
With bonds like family,
違いが分かり合えた
we could understand our differences
それぞれの
Each person has
輝きがあって
their own brilliance,
ハーモニー奏でるかな
so will we play a harmony?
手を繋いで共に
Holding hands together
夢の空の方へ
toward the sky of our dreams
精一杯
Let's give it
歓声をあげましょう
our all and cheer out loud
幸せを届けるんだ
We'll deliver happiness
どこにだって
to everywhere,
響けよ
let it resound!
新しい
Into the
舞台に飛び込んで
new stage, dive in
今
now!
リズムを整え直して
Fixing my rhythm again
ここに集めての音色が
The sounds gathered here
ブルーのハーモニーになって
Becoming a blue harmony
心の迷いが消えていく
The hesitation in my heart fades away
これからずっとこの自分のままで
Staying just as I am from now on
集まった声たちが
The voices that gathered
違っても 揺るがないと信じて
Even if they're different, believing they won't waver
ひとつになるアイデンティティ
Identities becoming one
Selamat pagi semua!
Good morning everyone!
お疲れ様でした！
Thank you for your hard work!
Selamat malam semua!
Good evening everyone!
また会う日まで
Until the day we meet again
我らエデンの星を統べる者、秘密結社holoX、推参！
We who rule the Planet Eden, Secret Society holoX, has arrived!
でござる！
Go-zaru!
機は熟した！2026年を待つ貴様ら、準備はいいか！
The time is ripe! You all waiting for 2026, are you ready!
Are you ready?
夜が深まる ほら Darkness
The night deepens, look, Darkness
ノアール 抱えた本領発揮
Carrying Noir, showing my true colors
縄に従え エド・インスティンクト
Obey the rope, Edo Instinct
まことに忍 サムライガール
Truly a ninja, Samurai Girl
予備知識ないけど？
No prior knowledge though?
ブルー・ヴェルトでShake it! Shake it!
In the Blue Welt, Shake it! Shake it!
テンプレもオッケー！
Templates are okay too!
君に届く ジャッジ! ジャッジ!
Reaching you, Judge! Judge!
悪の手のひら 踊りたくなる
Wanting to dance in the palm of evil
ほら君も 気づけばノリノリで
Look, you're also getting into the groove before you know it
どうしようもない どうしようもない
Helpless, helpless
落ちてく運命
Falling fate
ならしょうがない 混ぜて
Then it can't be helped, mix it
全部塗り替えよう
And repaint everything
XとXとXとXが 交差する真ん中で
Where X and X and X and X intersect right in the middle
NextとNextとNextとNext 体系はもう始まってる
Next and Next and Next and Next, the system has already begun
飛びな 飛びな 闇が呼ぶ方へ
Jump, jump, towards where the darkness calls
反復の暁闇エクスデス
Reiterating Pre-dawn Darkness Exodus
混沌としたこの世界を、我らholoX色に塗り替えるのだ！
We shall repaint this chaotic world in holoX colors!
皆の衆、刮目せよ！
Everyone, behold!
Yes My Dark!
アブソリュート・ダークネス・インフィニティ！
Absolute Darkness Infinity!
来年こそ世界征服！
Next year for sure, world domination!
マダム・ホークアイ。
Madam Hawkeye.
はい、今見てる皆さんはもうholoXerですよ。
Yes, all of you watching now are already holoXers.
シャチニウム・ボンバー！
Orcanium Bomber!
2026年もずっと一緒だよ。
Let's be together all through 2026 too.
風真流奥義 鏡開き！
Kazama-style Secret Technique: Mirror Opening!
一刀両断 叩き斬れ！
Cut them down with a single stroke!
どうしようもない どうしようもない
Helpless, helpless
落ちてく運命
Falling fate
ならしょうがない 混ぜて
Then it can't be helped, mix it
全部塗り替えよう
And repaint everything
刮目せよ！ XとXとXとXが 交差する真ん中で
Behold! Where X and X and X and X intersect right in the middle
NextとNextとNextとNext 体系はもう始まってる
Next and Next and Next and Next, the system has already begun
飛びな 飛びな 闇が呼ぶ方へ
Jump, jump, towards where the darkness calls
笑うのは holoXです
The ones who'll be laughing is holoX
はっはっはっ！我ら holoXの締めの一曲、堪能したか！
Hahaha! Did you enjoy holoX's final song!
Run Back 'Round
Up with the moonlight, down in the streetlights
Looking for a spotlight, making my move
I'm running, 行こう！
I'm running, let's go!
Days like a whirlwind, don't stop coming
Got me in a tailspin, what can I do?
Keep running, 行こう！
Keep running, let's go!
Lost and found, back to where I started
I won't stay down, trust me I can do it
I live life loud, take it to the limit
So stand up proud, now I'm gonna sing it
Run Back 'Round, it's a new beginning
I Run Back 'Round, got to keep believing
I Run Back 'Round, I know where I'm going
I Run Back 'Round, nothing's gonna stop me now
I'm gonna run back round
Sparks on paper, dreams in the distance
Got to be relentless, faster than sound
Keep running, 行こう！
Keep running, let's go!
Locked and loaded, 僕らは explosive
Locked and loaded, we are explosive
Swifter and lighter, 明日も get up brighter
Swifter and lighter, tomorrow too get up brighter
Faster than lightning, 全てが exciting
Faster than lightning, everything is exciting
Come on everybody, いつも歌
Come on everybody, always singing
Run Back 'Round, it's a new beginning
I Run Back 'Round, got to keep believing
I Run Back 'Round, I know where I'm going
I Run Back 'Round, nothing's gonna stop me now
I'm gonna run back round
走って、走って、走って
Run, run, run
I'm gonna run back round
始まるよ, coming around, 描いた dream is waiting
It's beginning, coming around, the dream I drew is waiting
I'm gonna run back round
Everybody, listen up everybody come on
HoloID, you guys ready?
To greet the new year? Hell yeah!
No time to waste! Let's get it started!
Slap by Step
万全なフレーズでキャッチアップして
Catch up with perfect phrases
困難だらけの人生だけど
In a life full of difficulties
十方にスラップして
Slapping in all directions
楽しんじゃおう
Let's have some fun
Fly like a feather soaring high
立ちはだかる壁なんて
Any wall that stands in the way
三枚おろしよ
Slice it up!
Fly like a feather soaring high
止まれないじゃなくて
It's not that I can't stop
止まらないんだ
It's that I won't stop
Slap by Step
迷わず一歩
One step without hesitation
私なりで
In my own way
隙あらばその瞬間に
At any gap, in that moment
歓声のシャワー浴びながら
While bathing in a shower of cheers
One two threeで心酔クラッシュして
Crashing with intoxication on one-two-three
止まらない現実を更新
Update the unstoppable reality
進めるライフ
Move life forward
震える宇宙を見て
See the shaking universe
歩く才色 / ヌランス・フロア
Walking on the brilliant / nuance floor
どんなヴェインな / 平手打ちを
Any kind of vain / slap...
ケチもはずかしがらないで
Don't be stingy or shy about it
似合っているさ / コンプレス・ステップ
It suits you, / this compress step
Clap your hands and stand up please
意気込んじゃっても / せばなるスレがソレさ
Even if you're enthusiastic, / that's just the way it goes
Clap your hands and stand up please
時代を奪え / ジタバタはノーサ
Seize the era, / no more flailing around
Wearing my teeth...
...and have no fear...
Ready to breakthrough...
姿...
Appearance...
キャッチ...
Catching...
違っても同じ思いだ / どこからでも
Even if we're different, we feel the same / no matter where from
Slap by step / 360度私なりで
Slap by step / 360 degrees, in my own way
突きあらば
If there's an opening...
その瞬間に感性がショーは今に
In that moment, sensitivity—the show is now
沼にハマっちゃえよ
Just fall into the depths
1 2 3 で真相 真理 クラッシュして
Crash truth and reality with a 1 2 3
今すぐね
Right now
私たちの色に染め上げた
Dyed in our colors
世界を見せつけて
Show off the world
皆様、今年もありがとうございましたですわ！
Everyone, thank you for this year!
ホロIDはもっともっと盛り上がるよ！
HoloID is going to get even more hyped!
ずっと見てて！
Keep watching!
来年もよろしくお願いします！
Please look forward to us next year too!
See you next year!
皆さん、森カリオペです！
Everyone, I'm Mori Calliope!
What's up Hololive English Myth coming right at you for a brand new year!
今年すごい盛り上がったね。
This year was really exciting.
来年もよろしく！
Looking forward to next year too!
We're gonna rock the world ten times harder next year.
You in? Next up, Ina!
Wah! Hello everyone, this is Ina!
Thank you so much for a really fun 2025.
今年すごく楽しかったです。
This year was a lot of fun.
来年もよろしくお願いしますね。
I look forward to working with you next year as well.
Yeah, let's go!
Next is Kiara!
Ha!
キケリキ！小鳥遊キアラです！
Kikiriki! I'm Takanashi Kiara!
キアラらしく盛り上がるぞ！
Let's get hyped, Kiara style!
Dankeschön! Next, come on!
Let's have fun in 2026 too!
Let's go! やりましょうか。
Let's go! Shall we start?
2026年もよろしく！
Best regards for 2026 too!
Alright, let's show them what we got!
There's an answer out there somewhere / When the muses whisper truth or dare
It's a fatefully tug of war / But no one's keeping score
Set a course and be tenacious / 'Cause the future is a game of chance
The chips are down but I'm a winner / I'll play until I win
I'm not gonna give up yet / The wheels of fortune circle back around
My future in the betting ring / A maze of outcomes drawn in golden strings
And through this tangled thread / I see what's up ahead
A wild chase, a better face / I've got to try my luck and spinning fate
Spin the wheel, let's see where it falls / Testing the limits and betting it all
Round and round, jumping into the circle / Over and over, a test of will
Though the game is never easy / And the outcome is a mystery
But these the fates we're betting on / Their threads unbroken
Called to life by flex and string / Casting lots together at the start of everything
I'm not gonna give up yet / It spins back round with every chance I get
Underneath this tangled thread,
the time has come for fate to change at last.
And if it's black or red,
I'm moving up ahead.
A perfect chance,
a daring dance.
I'll spin this web of fate with my own hands.
I'm taking fate into my hands.
Whoa, yeah.
Underneath this tangled thread, I see what's up ahead.
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
Hyper Jumpin'
Hyper Jumpin'!
飛び出せ Wow!
Jump out, Wow!
Come on baby 輝いて
Come on baby, shine bright
ハートキュンとパピア
Heart pounding and happy-a
Hyper Jumpin'!
有頂天の先まで
Until beyond the peak of ecstasy
もっともっと刺激が欲しいの
I want more and more stimulation
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
Hyper Jumpin'!
子供みたいにはしゃぐ方がお得でしょ
It's better to frolic like a child, right?
Take it up から這い上がっていくテンション
Tension crawling up from 'Take it up'
宵長が打ち返し捲るメンション
Mentions being thrown back and forth through the long night
カードを乗りこなして進むミッション
Mission progressing while mastering the cards
このままスピード加速して
Speeding up just like this
たどり着く先に何があるんだろう
I wonder what lies at our destination
止まらない気持ちは助走つけて
Gathering speed with these unstoppable feelings
次元を超えていこう
Let's go beyond dimensions
さあ Hyper Jumpin' 飛び跳ねよう
Come on, Hyper Jumpin', let's leap
ハイになって灰になるまで
Until we're high and turn to ash
テンション素敵な
A wonderful tension
Hyper Jumpin' 空の向こうまで
Hyper Jumpin' to the other side of the sky
もっともっと近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer
Whoa whoa whoa whoa
ドキドキしたい Gimme gimme gimme 愛
I want my heart to throb, give me give me love
もっともっと高く飛びたいの
I want to fly higher and higher
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
Hyper Jumpin'!
斜めから攻めていけ決意クエスチョン
Go on the offensive from an angle, a question of determination
ネガティブを切り裂いてくれるテンション
Tension that tears through the negative
残れるコメントと掛け合いセッション
A session of banter with the remaining comments
エイムを鍛えて狙い撃つフリクション
Friction that aims and shoots with trained aim
This one no no
No no ma ma ma
邪魔するノイズは打ち消せバンバンバン
Cancel out the distracting noise, bang bang bang
遊びたいだけ
I just want to play
味わい尽くして
Taste it all
笑い飛ばして
Laugh it off
蹴飛ばして
Kick it away
Kick it!
Jump around! Jump around!
このまま僕らは旅をして
We'll keep on traveling like this
たどり着く先に何があるんだろう
I wonder what lies at our destination
信じた未来とリンクして
Linking up with the future we believed in
次元を超えていこう
Let's go beyond dimensions
さあ！
Come on!
さあ Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Come on, Hyper Jumpin', let's jump over
ハイになって灰になるまで
Until we're high and turn to ash
テンション素敵な
A wonderful tension
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまで
Hyper Jumpin' to the other side of the sea
もっともっと近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer
Whoa whoa whoa whoa
ドキドキしたい Gimme gimme gimme 愛
I want my heart to throb, give me give me love
もっともっと高く飛びたいの
I want to fly higher and higher
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
目を覚ませ 目を開かして
Wake up, open your eyes
Dramatic XViltration
夢から抜け出して
Escape from the dream
世界が動き出す
The world starts to move
我らの蘇り
Our resurrection
鏡に映る
Reflected in the mirror
心に宿っている
Residing in the heart
小さい光
A small light
さあ　今も感じる
Come, I still feel it
どこか心の奥で
Somewhere deep in my heart
呼び覚ました
Awakened
忘れられない浮かぶメモリ
Unforgettable memories surfacing
今の自分になるその前に
Before I become who I am now
果てのない音色で迷い
Getting lost in an endless melody
そして黄昏が落ちてくるどこまでも
And the twilight falls, wherever it may be
引き締める鎖がまた　体を止めていた
The tightening chains had stopped my body again
躊躇い覚えてしまって　凍えていくの
Having learned hesitation, I am freezing
明日の向こう側には　未知なるエリア
Beyond tomorrow lies an unknown area
その境界線の先に待つのは
What awaits beyond that boundary line
壱語のはじめ
The beginning of the first word
目覚めは鳴らす
Awakening rings out
奈落の底へと　落ちていく
Falling to the bottom of the abyss
知覚さえ知らぬ
Unaware even of perception
時計の針の音
The sound of the clock hands
頼りなく残り
Weakly remaining
広がる海
The spreading sea
届くはずのない　知らない森の中に
Inside an unknown forest that shouldn't be reachable
宇宙を超え　逃げ場探して
Beyond space, searching for a place to escape
そんな過去もまだ　頭に響いている
Such a past as well, still echoing in my head
解けない鎖を断ち　切れないまま足掻き
Breaking unbreakable chains, struggling while unable to sever them
物語の始まり　探し続けたい
The beginning of the story, I want to keep searching for it
無情　一度きりの不甲斐ない　謎のようなことさ
Heartlessness, a one-time, pathetic, mystery-like thing
この体の中で目覚めた
Awakened inside this body
本当の姿
My true form
運命のカードが占う未来
The future predicted by the cards of fate
深層へ
To the depths
おまじない
Incantation
解き放つ鎖が消え　進めると信じて
The chains that set me free disappear, believing I can move forward
新しい自分になって　光の方へ
Becoming a new me, towards the light
遂に辿り着いた　未知なるエリア
Finally reached the unknown area
その境界線を超える日が来た
The day to cross that boundary has come
壱語の終わり
The end of the first word
信じ合う仲間と一緒に
Together with friends who believe in each other
挑戦の狼煙を上げよう
Let's raise the signal fire of challenge
終わらない　青春アーカイブ
Never-ending Seishun Archive
凡人なんて自称は捨てて　兵児！
Discard the self-proclaimed title of an ordinary person, Hey!
みんなで揃えば行けるじゃん
If we're all together, we can go, can't we?
青春アーカイブ
Seishun Archive
イケる 素敵 頑張れ 落ちて
You can do it, it's great, do your best, go for it
青春 感じていましょう 遊べ
Let's feel our youth, let's play
アッチュ！
Atchu!
成長した姿を見せたい
I want to show you how much I've grown
ビバ 完璧 本番はもっと 全力で
Viva! Perfect! In the real show, even more power!
ハイ！ ハイ！ ホォー！
Hi! Hi! Hoo!
大切な思い出
Precious memories
だってあるけどね まだ
There are some, but still
感傷に浸ってる暇はない
There's no time to soak in sentiment
今世紀最大の夏が始まる
The biggest summer of the century is starting
想像の果てにある高み
The heights at the end of imagination
勝ち取った景色は尊い
The scenery we won is precious
逃げるな 限界の壁 越えて
Don't run away, cross the wall of your limits
僕らはまだチャレンジャー Yeah!
We are still challengers, yeah!
冷たい声に溺れたって
Even if drowned out by cold voices
確かな爪をたぐり寄せるように
As if reaching out to grab a foothold
期待外れだと誰かが嘆く
Someone laments it's not what they expected
痛いと痛いがいつも戦う
Pain and pain are always fighting
プライドだけを頼りに抗う
Resisting, relying only on pride
自分を信じたい
I want to believe in myself
努力は報われる
Effort will be rewarded
笑いたい奴は笑ってろ
Let whoever wants to laugh, laugh
感傷に浸ってる暇はない
There's no time to soak in sentiment
今世紀最大の夏が始まる
The biggest summer of the century is starting
反響が足りない もっともっと
The echo isn't enough, more, more
後悔はさせない
I won't let you regret it
想像の果てにある高み
The heights at the end of imagination
勝ち取った景色は尊い
The scenery we won is precious
逃げるな 限界の壁 越えて
Don't run away, cross the wall of your limits
僕らはまだチャレンジャー Yeah!
We are still challengers, yeah!
夢見る空へ
Yumemiru Sora e
重ねた手はぎゅっと離さずに
Don't ever let go of our joined hands
行くよ 行こう 夢見る空へ
Here we go, let's go, to the sky of our dreams
窓越しに見上げた
Looking up through the window
とても小さな空
At a very small sky
ここで出会えたのは
Meeting here was
数えきれない奇跡
A series of countless miracles
繰り返した一歩が
The steps we repeatedly took
きらめきをつないで
Connected the sparkles
星のような笑顔
A smile like a star
導いた
Guided us
Day by day みんなの声が力になる
Day by day, everyone's voices become our strength
Stage by stage ここでそれぞれ目指すもの
Stage by stage, what we each aim for here
それぞれ描くもの
What we each portray
それぞれ願った夢へ
Towards the dreams we each wished for
重ねた手はぎゅっと離さずに
Don't ever let go of our joined hands
一人ひとり違う色で描き出すときめき
The excitement each of us paints in different colors
振り向くことなく真っ直ぐに
Go straight ahead without looking back
行くよ 行こう 夢見る空へ
Here we go, let's go, to the sky of our dreams
笑い合ったことや
The times we laughed together
尽きない我が儘
And our endless selfishness
思い出いっぱいなのに
Even though there are so many memories
あっという間の日々
The days passed in the blink of an eye
上書きじゃなくて
Not by overwriting
名前つけて保存
But by "Saving As"
どれも全部大事って 言い切れる
I can say for sure that every one of them is precious
1 4 All みんなの糧が力になる
1 for All, everyone's support becomes my strength
All 4 One 邪魔すぎるくらい
All for One, so much so that it's almost too much
笑顔がもう止まらない
The smiles just won't stop
思いは膨らんで行く
My feelings keep growing
重ねた今 ギュッと噛み締めた
I cherish this moment we've built together
一人ひとり違う声で
With each of our different voices
歌えば広がる
As we sing, it spreads far and wide
風を感じたらまっすぐに
If I feel the wind, I'll go straight ahead
行くよ 行こう
Let's go, let's head out
夢見る空へ
Toward the sky of our dreams
憧れ 手を伸ばし
Reaching out toward my aspiration
掴み取った その光が
The light that I've grasped
いつの日か
Will one day
また誰かの憧れに
Become an aspiration for someone else
変わる
In turn
繋ぎ合おう
Let's connect it all together
重ねた手は ギュッと離さずに
Holding our hands tight, never letting go
一人ひとり違う色で
With each of our different colors
描き出すときめき
Drawing out this excitement
出会ったすべてにありがとう
Thank you for everything that I've encountered
奇跡だって起こし続け
We'll keep making miracles happen
ずっと ずっとそばにいるよ
I'll be by your side forever and ever
行くよ 行こう
Let's go, let's head out
夢見る空へ
Toward the sky of our dreams
ホロライブゲーマーズ！
Hololive Gamers!
We are GAMERS!!!!
ホロライブゲーマーズだよ！
We're Hololive Gamers!
みんなお待たせ
Sorry to keep you waiting, everyone
We are GAMERS!!!!
楽しむ準備は
Are you ready to have some fun?
できてるよね？
You are, right?
せーの！
One, two!
We are GAMERS!!!!
コンコンきつねが
The kon-kon fox
登場 白上
Has arrived, Shirakami!
ケモ耳白髪 フブキで！
Animal ears and white hair, it's Fubuki!
突っ込んじゃ始まらない
If you don't jump in, nothing starts
君もスコーン部に
You should also join
入部しなさい
The Sukon-bu club!
コンコン絶好調
Kon-kon, in top form!
頂戴
Give it to me!
Aじゃなくて 得意はMC
Not A, my specialty is MCing
赤井ノリきった声が推し
A high-spirited red voice is my pick
ミオさーん！
Mio-saan!
ウチウチウチだよ！
It's me, me, me!
大神ミオだよ！
I'm Ookami Mio!
黒髪ケモ耳 大神！ ミオーン！
Black hair and animal ears, Ookami! Mioon!
突っ込んで止めます
I'll jump in and stop it
ライザーママ
Raizaa mama
笑い出すと止まらない
Once I start laughing, I can't stop
ゲラゲラ
Giggle giggle
ツマに実はぽんこつ？
Actually a klutz at the edge?
壊しステップしちゃおっと
I think I'll do a break dance step
タロット占いでみる未来
The future seen through Tarot readings
ホラーゲームは
I don't want to
やりたくない！
Play horror games!
4人揃えばゲーマーズ最強
With the four of us, Gamers are the strongest
君も朝晩 ヨピタッシュ
You too, morning and night, Yopitasshu
クリアを目指してレベル上げ
Leveling up aiming for the clear
今日は 何プレイしよう？
What shall we play today?
君のハートも コーデしちゃう
I'll even coordinate your heart
選択をして シミュレーション
Making choices, a simulation
初見も古参も 大歓迎
Newcomers and veterans are all welcome
やっぱ ゲームは 楽しめ！
After all, games are for having fun!
W-E-A-M-E-R-S
We are GAMERS!!!!
おかゆー！
Okayuu!
行くよもぐもぐ 猫又おかゆ
Here I go, munch munch, Nekomata Okayu
おにぎりおにぎり はいっどーぞ
Onigiri, onigiri, here you go
キラキラふらふら 承認猫だもん
Sparkling and drifting, I'm an acknowledged cat
んー？そっか 僕でよくない？
Hmm? Is that so? Isn't it fine if it's me?
まったりゆっくり 跳ねるリズム
Chilling and taking it slow, a bouncing rhythm
天衣無縫 おかゆいずむ
Flawless, Okayu-ism
前代未聞 リーズナブル
Unprecedented, reasonable
毎日 僕と一緒に！
Every day, together with me!
ころねー！
Koronee!
おあよー指指 ワンワン！
Good morning, yubi yubi, bow-wow!
パン派の 戌神ころね
I'm Inugami Korone, a bread person
キャバリアキング チャールズスパニエル
Cavalier King Charles Spaniel
結構アグレッシブ
Quite aggressive
なまらイントネーション 荒れるリアクション
Intense intonation, wild reactions
まずは指を 捧げてくれる？
First, will you offer me your fingers?
はい視聴 分かったな
Okay, viewer, you got that?
本メッセージ オッケー
This message is okay
好物のレトロゲー お届け！
Delivering my favorite retro games!
世に有象無象あれば毛まず最高
If there are all sorts of things in this world, beasts are the best
フラッグ立てれば即回収
If you plant a flag, collect it immediately
エイム鍛えて狙い撃ち
Train your aim and take the shot
今日は何をプレイしよう？
What shall we play today?
君のハートを回復しちゃう
I'll heal your heart
ワクワクするぜこの感情
This feeling gets me excited
大好きっていうか辞められない
I love it, or rather, I can't stop
だってゲームが好きなんだもん
Because I just love games
突然ですが、ボーナスチャレンジの時間です！
Suddenly, it's time for the Bonus Challenge!
大きな声でレスポンスして、高得点を狙いましょう！
Respond with a loud voice and let's aim for a high score!
Are you ready?
せーの、コンコン！
Ready, Kon Kon!
コンコン！
Kon Kon!
せーの、ミョーンミョーン！
Ready, Myon Myon!
ミョーンミョーン！
Myon Myon!
せーの、もぐもぐ！
Ready, Mogu Mogu!
もぐもぐ！
Mogu Mogu!
せーの、ゆびゆび！
Ready, Yubi Yubi!
ゆびゆび！
Yubi Yubi!
せーの、コンコン！
Ready, Kon Kon!
コンコン！
Kon Kon!
せーの、ミョーンミョーン！
Ready, Myon Myon!
ミョーンミョーン！
Myon Myon!
せーの、もぐもぐ！
Ready, Mogu Mogu!
もぐもぐ！
Mogu Mogu!
せーの、ゆびゆび！
Ready, Yubi Yubi!
ゆびゆび！
Yubi Yubi!
世に有象無象あれば毛まず最高
If there are all sorts of things in this world, beasts are the best
上手くいかなくってもコンティニュー
Even if it doesn't go well, continue
全クリするまで諦めない
Don't give up until the 100% completion
エンディングを見に行こう
Let's go see the ending
君のハートも攻略しちゃう
I'll conquer your heart too
選択をしてシミュレーション
Make a choice and simulate
初見も古参も大乱世
Newcomers and veterans alike in a great chaotic age
やっぱゲームは楽しいね！
Games really are fun, aren't they!
We are Gamers!
こうして２０２５年の幕が閉じるのであった
And so, the curtain falls on the year 2025.
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make our fresh heart-throbs resound
最高の時間　最高の仲間と
The best time, with the best comrades
きらめきに乗って
Riding on the sparkle
イェーイ！
Yay!
覚えてるかな　最初の歌
Do you remember? Our first song
懐かしいね
It brings back memories
私　声が　震えていた
My voice was trembling
懐かしい
Memories...
あの日から続く未来は
The future that followed from that day
みんなと掴んだ　今日だよ
Is the today we grabbed together
もっと もっと もっと もっと
More, more, more, more
加速するハート
My accelerating heart
一緒に行こうよ
Let's go together
どこまでも
Anywhere and everywhere
Are you ready?
準備はOK?
拓け 夢の 扉を
Open the door to your dreams
1・2・3 キラメキライダー
1, 2, 3 Kirameki Rider!
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make our fresh heart-throbs resound
最高の時間　最高の仲間と
The best time, with the best comrades
ここにいるよ　見つけてくれたから
I'm here, because you found me
君に会いたくてやってきたんだ
I came here because I wanted to see you
みんなで歌おう
Let's all sing
終わらないメロディー
An unending melody
きらめきに乗って
Riding on the sparkle
キラメキライダー☆
Kirameki Rider☆
君の心が幸せに染まるように
May your heart be dyed in happiness
重ねていくハーモニー
As our harmonies overlap
キラメキ纏って
Adorned with brilliance
歌い続けたいな
I want to keep singing
踊り続けたいな
I want to keep dancing
そんな願いはわがままでもいいでしょ？
Is it okay if those wishes are a bit selfish?
だって楽しすぎて
Because it's so much fun
もう止まらない
I can't stop anymore
輝くステージでもっともっと
On this shining stage, more and more
いくよー！
Here we go!
ずっと！
Forever!
嬉しい 楽しい 愛しい だけじゃ語れない
Happy, fun, beloved... those words alone can't describe it
今も 今も 悩みはあるけれど
Even now, even now, there are worries, but...
ここにいるよ 私
I'm right here
ここにいるよ
君と同じ世界を見つめて
Gazing at the same world as you
いくよー！
Here we go!
キラメキライダー☆
Kirameki Rider☆
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let the fresh excitement echo out
最高の時間
The best time
最高の仲間と
With the best friends
ここにいるよ
I'm right here
見つけてくれたから
Because you found me
君に会いたくてやってきたんだ
I came here because I wanted to see you
みんなで歌おう
Let's all sing together
終わらないメロディ
An endless melody
キラメキに乗って
Riding on the brilliance
キラメキ纏って
Adorned with brilliance
イエーイ！
Yay!
2025年もあと少し！みんな盛り上がってるー？
Only a little bit of 2025 left! Is everyone hyped up?
今回はカウントダウンライブ！
This is the Countdown Live!
あれあれー？コメントの熱量なんだか少なくなーい？
Wait, what? Isn't the comment enthusiasm a bit low?
まだまだ足りない！コンコンコーン！
It's not nearly enough! Kon-kon-kon!
電脳ぴゅあ推し大宣言
Cyberspace Pure Oshi Grand Declaration
こんこんこんこん！
Kon-kon-kon-kon!
浮気は許しません
I won't forgive cheating
私だけに尽くしてね
Devote yourself only to me, okay?
私だけにひきつけ中
Keep your focus only on me
よそ見はヤダヤダ妥協状
Looking away is a no-no, no compromises!
チュンチュン 構って
Tweet-tweet, pay attention to me
ちょちょちょ 誰もよそ見したら ボンボンボン 滅
Wait-wait-wait, if anyone looks away, boom-boom-boom, destroyed!
メロメロ メラップ
Mellow-mellow melody
ぷぷぷらっぷ
Poo-poo-poo rap
みんなで推しましょ アッププ
Let's all push together, up-pu-pu
ふいに歌うから離さないでしょ？
I'll sing out of the blue, so you won't let go, right?
よそ見はダメ！本当にイヤイヤ
No looking away! I really hate it
いつも見て見て 私待ってる
Look at me, look at me always, I'm waiting
あなたが教えてくれる 愛情のセンター
You're the one who shows me the center of affection
私を支える 永遠さ
It's the eternity that supports me
ラビラビラヴ 推し抜く時 チュマチュマ
Lovely-lovely love, when you're a devoted fan, kiss-kiss
とってもとってもとってもとっても愛してほしい
I want you to love me very, very, very, very much
ハッピーハッピーハッピー 最高のキュンキュン
Happy, happy, happy, the best heart-throbbing
はっきりはっきりはっきり
Clearly, clearly, clearly
ここテンション ピコピコ
Here, the tension goes beep-beep
気持ちのバロメーター超上がる
My heart's barometer is rising sky-high
大好き 大好き 大好き
I love you, I love you, I love you
もう本当に本当に本当に本当に 分かってね
Please, really, really, really, really understand me
おーいみんな！ここまでついてこれてる？この後もこの調子で行くよー！
Hey everyone! Are you keeping up? Let's keep this momentum going!
ちょっと待って何で他の子褒めるの？
Wait a second, why are you praising other girls?
よそ見はプンプン
Looking away makes me mad!
私以外も気になってるでしょ
You're interested in others besides me, aren't you?
ありえないの！ありえない！
That's unacceptable! Unacceptable!
パンパン 他の子にちょちょちょだめ
Clap-clap, no, no, no, not for other girls
よそ見したよね？嘘マジ無理
You looked away just now, didn't you? No way, I really can't deal with that
ピュア落ちしちゃう私をチュンチュン 指切りしてよ 針千本！
I'll fall for you purely, tweet-tweet, Pinky swear, or you'll swallow a thousand needles!
心変わりしたら本当に 拗ねる 怒る 泣いちゃうからね
If you have a change of heart, I'll really sulk, get mad, and cry, you know?
推し変はしてないね？ 私だけに尽くして...
You haven't changed your bias, right? Devote yourself only to me...
るー！
...e!
だってほら コメントが愛に溢れている
Because look, the comments are overflowing with love
必死のHP 見る見る回復
My desperate HP is recovering in the blink of an eye
時空へ満ちたパワーチャージ
Power charging, filling the space-time
ごめごめごめ ちょごめごめごめ
Sorry-sorry-sorry, a little sorry-sorry-sorry
ラビラビラヴ 推し抜く時 チュマチュマ
Lovely-lovely love, when you're a devoted fan, kiss-kiss
いっぱいいっぱいいっぱいいっぱい愛してほしい
I want you to love me a lot, a lot, a lot, a lot
ハッピーハッピーハッピー 最高のキュンキュン
Happy, happy, happy, the best heart-throbbing
もううっとりうっとりうっとり 分かってね
Already entranced, entranced, entranced, understand me
こりに　こりに　こりに　こりに...
Korini korini korini korini...
私のため日々日々お仕事励んでくれてありがとう
Thanks for working hard at your job every day for my sake
もしもしも愛しい
If, if I am beloved
絶対絶対絶対...
Absolutely, absolutely, absolutely...
お願いね
Please
このこのこのこの
This, this, this, this
うっ！このこのこのこの
Ugh! This, this, this, this
このこのこのこの
This, this, this, this
銀河の果てまで推してほしい
I want you to support me to the ends of the galaxy
同じ未来を見ていたい
I want to see the same future
あの夢手にしたい
I want to grasp that dream
それぞれ違った心で
With our different hearts
走り出そう
Let's start running
Shiny Smily Story
作詞：金丸佳史 (onetrap)
作曲・編曲：中野領太 (onetrap)
Shiny Smily Story
Lyrics: Yoshifumi Kanamaru (onetrap)
Composition/Arrangement: Ryota Nakano (onetrap)
どこ見ても真っ暗な場所に芽生えていた
It budded in a place where everything was pitch black
ほんの小さな希望にこの瞳奪われた
My eyes were captivated by a tiny speck of hope
不安で揺れる心をうまくチューニングして
Tuning my heart that wavers with anxiety
ほんの小さな勇気を振り絞っていたんだよ
I was squeezing out a tiny bit of courage
あきらめの文字手放して進む
Letting go of the word "surrender" as I move forward
苦しい時も　もう私は一人じゃないから
Because even in painful times, I'm not alone anymore
だからこそ夢追いかけたい
That's why I want to chase my dreams
ワクワク止まらない
The excitement won't stop
想像超えていく世界見せてあげる
I'll show you a world that exceeds your imagination
アクセスしてみたい
I want to try accessing it
後悔なんてさせない
I won't let you have any regrets
それぞれ違った心で走り出そう
Let's start running with our different hearts
空想の空に輝く眩しい想いは
The dazzling feelings shining in the imaginary sky
見たことのない光をリアルに届けるよ
Will deliver a light you've never seen to reality
いつも聞こえるエールはここにキャプチャーして
Capturing the cheers I always hear right here
また新しい光を探したくなるよ
It makes me want to search for new light again
君の笑顔は綻びて進む
Your smile blooms as we advance
悲しい時に見返すよ　力が沸くから
I'll look back at it when I'm sad, because it gives me strength
胸を張って夢追いかけたい
I want to chase my dreams with pride
奇跡のストーリー一緒に作ろう
Let's create a miracle story together
終わらない夢を　誰一人欠かさない
An unending dream, without missing a single person
曖昧なこの世界
In this vague world
それぞれ違った心で彩れ
Paint it with our different hearts
楽しい時も
In happy times
寂しい時も
In lonely times
信じ合えるものがある
There's something we can believe in together
結び目にこの鼓動鳴らし続けたい
I want to keep this heartbeat sounding at the knot
モノクロな世界に溢れ出すよ　絵具たち
The paints are overflowing into the monochrome world
憧れの舞台立ちたい
I want to stand on the stage I admire
真っ直ぐ輝きたい
I want to shine straightforwardly
時に涙してまた笑い合いたい
Sometimes crying, and wanting to laugh together again
同じ未来を見ていたい
I want to see the same future
あの夢手にしたい
I want to grasp that dream
踏み出そう奇跡の一歩を
Let's take a miracle step forward
息切らして夢追いかけたい
Out of breath, I want to chase my dreams
ワクワク止まらない
The excitement won't stop
想像超えていく世界見せてあげる
I'll show you a world that exceeds your imagination
アクセスしてみな
Try accessing it
後悔なんてここにない
There are no regrets here
それぞれ違った心でつくろう
Let's create it with our different hearts
みんな、コークは持ったかな？
Everyone, do you have your Cokes?
準備した！乾杯するー！
I'm ready! Let's toast!
こらこら早いよラプちゃん。
Hey now, too early, Lapu-chan.
避けるな！当たる！
Don't dodge! It'll hit!
年越しのタイミングで、みんなで乾杯ってするんだよ。
We're all going to toast together at the turn of the year.
やだやだ、もう喉カラカラ。
No, no, my throat is already parched.
楽しみだね。
I'm looking forward to it.
ねぇ、みこさん。みこさん？
Right, Miko-san? Miko-san?
いやー、いいライブだったねー。
Wow, that was a great live show.
おつかれー。イェーイ。
Good job. Yay.
この後どうする？ご飯食べる？
What should we do now? Want to eat?
いやー、どこも混んでんじゃない？
Well, everywhere's probably crowded, right?
確かに。もう帰りますかね。
True. Should we just head home?
あ、運転手さん、まっすぐね。
Oh, driver, go straight, please.
お、お。
Oh, oh.
おい！
Hey!
お前ら！何帰ってんだ！
You guys! Why are you going home?!
乾杯！乾杯！
Cheers! Cheers!
フブちゃんたちがついてきてる。
Fubu-chan and the others are following us.
おろおろ、フブスも寂しくなっちゃったのかねぇ。
Oh dear, maybe Fubusu got lonely too.
待てー！
Wait!
なんか怒ってない？
Don't they seem kind of angry?
おえ？あ、やばい。あのいたずらバレたかな？
Eh? Oh no. Did they find out about that prank?
あはは。やりすぎだったかなぁ。
Ahaha. Maybe we went too far.
やばいかも。運転手さん、ごめん。
This might be bad. Driver, sorry.
うおおおー！
Waaaaagh!
みこのドラテクで逃げるぞ！
I'll escape with my driving techniques!
うわー！うわー！
Whoa! Whoa!
あ、来た。
Ah, they're here.
おおー。
Whoa.
すごいすごい！
Amazing, amazing!
うおー！
Whoa!
フブちゃんごめんて、もういたずらしないから。
I'm sorry Fubu-chan, I won't play pranks anymore.
だめだよみこみこ、反省しなさい。
No good, MikoMiko, reflect on what you've done.
お前も共犯だろうが！
You were an accomplice too!
何の話だ。おい。
What are you talking about? Hey.
二人ともこれ持って。
Both of you, take this.
何するの？
What are we doing?
もうすぐ新年だよ。
It's almost the New Year.
おおー！
Ohhh!
乾杯ー！
Cheers!
あけましておめでとう！
Happy New Year!
今年もよろしくね。
Happy New Year to you too.
うわぁ！
Whoa!
最高の一杯！
The best drink ever!
そういえば、いたずらって何なの？
By the way, what was the prank?
あ、それね。
Oh, that.
フブさんのへそ、増やしたんだよ。
We multiplied Fubu-san's belly buttons.
恐怖！
Terrifying!
この後は、コカ・コーラと一緒に、スペシャルライブステージ！
Next up, a special live stage with Coca-Cola!
イェーイ！
Yay!
SPECIAL STAGE
澄ますずっと僕らの奇跡が
I'll listen closely so our miracle
途切れないように歌うんだ　もっと高く大きな声で
will never cease, singing with an even louder, higher voice
Prism Melody
Words, Music, Arrangement: 5u5h1
聞こえてた　何かが始まるサイン",
I heard it, the sign that something is starting
集まって気付けば　鼓動奏でた
We gathered, and before I knew it, our heartbeats were in sync
夢に見るだけじゃもう　足りないでしょう？
Just dreaming isn't enough anymore, is it?
君を待ってる世界があるよ
There's a world out there waiting for you
楽しい予感にほら　飛び込んじゃえばいい
Just dive into that feeling of excitement
ときめきは止められないから
Because this heart-pounding feeling can't be stopped
走ろう
Let's run
連れて行くよ光の真ん中　夢の先へ羽ばたける
I'll take you to the center of the light, we can soar beyond our dreams
勇気は君の願い　みんなで繋いだこの奇跡が
Courage is your wish, and this miracle we've linked together
途切れないように歌うんだ　もっと高く大きな声で
will never cease, singing with an even louder, higher voice
答えとか理屈に惑わされて
Confused by answers and logic
彷徨っても戻ってこれる場所があった
Even if I wandered, there was a place I could return to
自由に行き交う僕らは旅人
We are travelers, moving freely back and forth
願いだけが道標だよ
Only our wishes are our guideposts
夢の色が変わっても　変わらないメロディ
Even if the colors of our dreams change, the melody remains the same
君のために　僕らのために
For you, for us
歌おう
Let's sing
そうさきっと僕らの奇跡は　終わらないよ
That's right, our miracle will surely never end
涙さえきっかけに変えていこう
Let's turn even our tears into opportunities
信じてくれる仲間と一緒に
Together with friends who believe in me
どこへだって飛び出していこう　もっと遠く空へ
Let's leap out into the world, even further into the sky
未来の僕らに まだ見ぬ君に
To our future selves, to you we haven't seen yet
伝えたいこと たくさんあるんだ
There's so much I want to tell you
浮かべた今は 当たり前なんかじゃない
This moment we've envisioned is not just ordinary
翼を広げさあ今 飛ぼう
Spread your wings, now let's fly
Take my heart 連れていくよ 光の真ん中
Take my heart, I'll take you to the center of the light
夢の先へ はばたける 勇気は君の願い
To the end of the dream, the courage to flap our wings is your wish
みんなで繋いだ この奇跡が
This miracle we've all connected
途切れないように 歌うんだ もっと高く 大きな声で
I'll sing so it never stops, even higher, with a loud voice
僕らの未来へと どこまでも響け
Towards our future, let it echo everywhere
Prism Melody
Show Them (Who You Are)
Once you just forget about the past
'Cause in time it will never matter
But the love we had I'm hoping it will last
Bersama kita t'lah lewati
Together we have passed
Tawa dan canda jadi memori
Laughter and jokes become memories
Pastikan harinya cerah di masa nanti
Ensure the day is bright in the future
Do what you were meant to do
For it's time to make it true
Together we can all stand
Your hand in my hand
Forever hand in hand
Wujudkan mimpi genggamlah yang kau cari
Realize the dream, grab what you seek
Terpancarkan la la la la
Radiated la la la la
Pancarkan sendiri
Radiate yourself
It's time to show them who you are
Just shout it from the mountain high
To the sky we go, we go
Bersama kita t'lah lewati
Together we have passed
Tawa dan canda jadi memori
Laughter and jokes become memories
Pastikan harinya cerah di masa nanti
Ensure the day is bright in the future
Cerahmu nanti
Your brightness later
Do what you were meant to do
For it's time to make it true
Together we can all stand
Your hand in my hand
Forever hand in hand
Wujudkan mimpi genggamlah yang kau cari
Realize the dream, grab what you seek
Terpancarkan la la la la
Radiated la la la la
Pancarkan sendiri
Radiate yourself
Go so far
Fly and show them who you are
Always sing it la la la la
Be who you meant to be
Show Them (Who You Are)
Dan tak takut
And not afraid
Karena takkan ada akhirnya
Because it will never end
Semua kan baik saja
Everything will be just fine
Harapan baru denganmu
A new hope with you
Tajam lurus ke depan
Sharp and straight ahead
Tuk mulai bermimpi...
To start dreaming...
...genggamlah yang kau cari
...hold onto what you seek
Dan kita kan la-la-la, la-la-la
And we will la-la-la, la-la-la
Kau takkan sendiri
You won't be alone
Show them and travel far
Run and show them who you are
I'll be singing la-la-la, la-la-la
Kau takkan pernah sendiri
You will never be alone
It's time to show them who you are
Just shout it from the mountain high
To the sky we go, we go, oh
All for One
Just look around and see
It's so incredible
So many smiles in this sea of light
Take one step with me and you'll be dazzled
There's magic in the air tonight
The hours zoom zoom zoom, my heart goes boom boom boom
The world is brighter because you believe in me
Let's shout it loud loud loud, our time is right now
We're on the edge of destiny
For a moment I can dream with you
Every miracle we hope for might come true
We come together reaching out from far away
And suddenly you're here by my side
When our voices and hearts unite
We're gonna shine bright together, we're all for one
Let's sing all for one
The thrill of happiness is all around us
Jump in 'cause it's all for one, let's sing all for one
We're on our way to good times, good vibes
We'll treasure this day the rest of our lives (hey!)
All that we waited for, the dream we're striving toward
We're singing all for one, all for one
Some things in motion, get up it starts a celebration
Come see the wonders here beyond imagination
We're joining hands for the world to see
Feel the love and the energy
The hours zoom zoom zoom, my heart goes boom boom boom
A dizzy whirlwind of dreams and reality
Let's shout it loud loud loud, our time is right now
We're here together finally
Every moment takes my breath away
There's a feeling here that words cannot convey
We hear the rhythm and we rise to meet the song
And suddenly our hearts beat as one
Every voice ringing loud and clear
So glad to be here together, we're all for one
Let's sing all for one
We'll sing in harmony and we'll be happy
Jump in 'cause it's all for one, let's sing all for one
Keep up the hype, it's good times, good vibes
Remember this night the rest of our lives (hey!)
Raise up your hands and sway, your light will lead our way
We're shining all for one, all for one
Stomp in your memories, your joy and your hope
We'll gather and we'll sing upon this endless road
Feel the music in your passion is on
We're right here right now, so let the good times roll
Every time that I'm with you
I could swear it's like a wish is coming true
So I believe in you if you believe in me
Together we can chase all our dreams
1, 2, 3, 4, 5!
When our voices and hearts unite
We're gonna shine bright together, we're all for one
Let's sing all for one
The thrill of happiness is all around us
Jump in 'cause it's all for one, let's sing all for one
We're on our way to good times, good vibes
We'll treasure this day the rest of our lives (hey!)
All that we waited for, the dream we're striving toward
We're singing all for one, all for one
皆さん明けましておめでとうございます！
Happy New Year, everyone!
おめでとうー！
Happy New Year!
ReGLOSSのWe are...メドレーです
This is the "We are ReGLOSS" medley.
ここからはホロライブデバイス、コラボステージです！聞いてください、FG ROADSTER by ReGLOSS。
From here, it's the hololive DEV_IS collaboration stage! Please listen to "FG ROADSTER" by ReGLOSS.
搭載V8エンジン　第7感持ってろ現時点　ロックするこの世界と全人類　この5人でゲームをチェンジ
Equipped with a V8 engine, keep your 7th sense for now. Locking onto this world and all humanity, we five will change the game.
唸る4輪発進全部　皆さんサンキュー三欄比　アイズル似た者の探訪　取る一番ここからズラ
Roaring 4-wheel start, thank you everyone. Exploring similar souls, we'll take the lead from here.
エスコート超えて頂点　チャンスもセットだ当然　登り上げる頂天　ステップ踏んでく昇天
Beyond escorting to the peak, chances are set, of course. Rising to the top, stepping into ascension.
乗り込めFG ROADSTER　特殊部隊集合能力者　この歴史なほら超豪華　ぶっちぎりで置き去り降伏者
Get in the FG ROADSTER, a special forces assembly of the gifted. Look at this history, so luxurious. Pulling ahead and leaving those surrendering behind.
今高速でぶち抜いていく大気圏　エンジンからジェットの炎揺れている開基へ
Now blasting through the atmosphere at high speed. From the engine, jet flames are flickering toward the origin.
眼下に広がる大地へ越えていく回帰線　バックミラーにビッグブルーが映ってるIB M-FIRE
To the land spreading below, crossing the tropic. Big blue reflected in the rearview mirror, IBM-FIRE.
打ち上げたいから飛んでく宇宙船　この年代口果てないで　銀河に推し旅等
Wanna blast off, so the spaceship flies. Don't let this era end, an 'oshi' journey to the galaxy.
増えてるでっかいビジョン　燃えてるメンバー一同　ただいま現在進行形　越えてく世界規模
A growing huge vision, all members are on fire. Right now, in progress, going global.
空はずのワンスター　心臓がモンスター　エリアズ足りな　FGパーティな
The sky-should-be one star, heart is a monster. Areas aren't enough, it's an FG party.
光るディスコモンスター　ヘビーブースター　目覚めてく本能　青い炎
Shining disco monster, heavy booster. Awakening instinct, blue flame.
V-M-S Let's go out　突き抜ける風0から　空まで　トラまで　走るFG ROADSTER　唸るブースター　ログ残して見　今チェイスミー
V-M-S Let's go out, wind cutting through from zero. To the sky, to the tiger, driving the FG ROADSTER. Roaring booster, leave a log and see, now chase me.
明けましておめでとうございます！
Happy New Year!
ここからは私たちFlow Glowが、ReGLOSS先輩の「フィーリングラデーション」をかまさせていただきます！
From here, we, Flow Glow, will perform ReGLOSS-senpai's "Feeling Gradation"!
ニコタンが来た！
Nikotan is here!
セクシーにいくぞ、ショッピショマ！
Going sexy, shoppishoma!
エンズデカイ、レッツゴー！がんばるぞー！
Ends de kai, let's go! Let's do our best!
ジャマしちゃいけないな、ビビ
Can't let them get in the way, Vivi.
私の音に、おいで！
Come to my sound!
ハイポップなステップ刻んで　紐解いていくシチュ
Carving high-pop steps, unraveling the situation.
様変わりしてショウタイム　全然悪くないイマジネーション
Transforming showtime, not a bad imagination at all.
視界の霧は晴れわたって　悲しみには別れを告げ
The fog in sight clears up, bidding farewell to sadness.
酸いも甘いも中に放り出して　滲む空ピンクはバラ色
Throw in the sour and sweet, the blurring sky is rose-pink.
どれだけ上手く見せようとしても　君がいなければ何の意味もない
No matter how well I try to show off, if you're not there, it means nothing.
かすり傷すらつかない幻想　針の落ちないレコードのさ
A fantasy without even a scratch, like a record where the needle won't drop.
赤い瞳（め）止めてね色を　追い風にして　Come let’s run
Stop those red eyes, the color, with a tailwind, Come let's run.
誘（いざな）って吹き荒れる　向かい風にも心　靡かせて
Invite and blow, let your heart flutter even in the headwind.
飛び立って　To the future　ライン引いたって終わりじゃない
Take flight, To the future, even if a line is drawn, it's not the end.
ときめいてしまえば　瞬く間に広がる解放感
If you get excited, a sense of liberation spreads in an instant.
一つ一つ全てがドラマ　街も浴びたデベリスタライト
Each and every thing is a drama, the city bathed in DEV_IS starlight.
変わり映え色づくパノラマ　満ち溢れるフィーリングラデーション
A colorful panorama that changes, overflowing feeling gradation.
飛び立って　You make me up　恐れるものはない　Mr. Starlight
Take flight, You make me up, there is nothing to fear, Mr. Starlight.
綺麗（きれ）いださ夜明けが　透明な明日を照らすよ
How beautiful, the dawn will illuminate a transparent tomorrow.
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you very much!
最後の曲は、Our Bright Parade!
The last song is "Our Bright Parade"!
イェーイ！
Yay!
Our Bright Parade
作詞・作曲・編曲：堀江晶太
Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement: Shota Horie
パレード　パレード　パレード　輝くんだよ　呼び合う声を合図に
Parade, parade, parade, let it shine. With our calling voices as the signal.
パレパレパレ 探しに行く
Parade, parade, parade! Let's go find it
スカートは何回だって
No matter how many times my skirt...
ただ 独り言 続いた
I just kept talking to myself
ただ 始まりたくて走った
I just ran because I wanted to start
遠く 暗がりに灯った
A light flickered far away in the dark
それは 眩しすぎた名前
That was a name that shone too brightly
それは 優しすぎる思い出
Those are memories that are far too kind
もっと 近づけと手を伸ばした
I reached out to get closer
思いがけず 結び合った
Unexpectedly, we were joined together
ほら 今 迷子はいなくなった
Look, now no one is lost anymore
パレパレパレ 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade! We're gonna shine!
悔しさも愛おしさも 全部おいで
Frustration and endearment—bring it all along
風 夢 跳ね 飛び立てるさ
The wind, our dreams, and wings—we can fly
ささやかな祈りは光
A modest prayer becomes a light
終わりなき陽射し
An endless sunlight
君を見つけたこと 胸を張れるよ
Finding you is something I can be proud of
ここから これから
From here on out, from this moment on
アワー ブライト パレパレパレ
Our Bright Parade, parade, parade!
まだ 頼りない予感を
With this still-uncertain premonition
歌う 恥ずかしくって泣いた
I sing; I cried out of embarrassment
誰も 溶けぬ日 まさに
On a day where no one dissolves, indeed
いつか また会える おまじない
Is a charm to ensure we'll meet again
あの日 手の中に始まった
On that day, it began in our hands
ストーリー 数え切れない言葉
A story, with words beyond counting
震えるような思いじゃないさ
It's not just a feeling that makes me tremble
ほら 今 僕らを一つと呼ぼう
Look, now let's call us 'one'
パレパレパレ 美しいんだよ
Parade, parade, parade! It's beautiful!
許し合える切なさ 夜はきらめく
The sadness of mutual forgiveness makes the night sparkle
雨 晴れ パレ 混ざり合う空
Rain, sunshine, parade—all mixing in the sky
ふさわしい旅路は 君と歩くのさ
The journey that suits me best is the one I walk with you
君と歩くのだ
I'm walking with you
「ただいま」を聞けば 「おかえり」って叫ぶよ
If I hear 'I'm home,' I'll shout back 'Welcome back!'
当たり前じゃないか
Isn't that obvious?
パレパレパレ 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade! We're gonna shine!
暗がりを満たすのは 君だ 僕だ
What fills the darkness is you and me
パレパレパレ 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade! We're gonna shine!
悔しさも愛おしさも 全部おいで
Frustration and endearment—bring it all along
風 夢 跳ね 飛び立てるさ
The wind, our dreams, and wings—we can fly
ささやかな祈りは光
A modest prayer becomes a light
終わりなき陽射し
An endless sunlight
君と飛び込んでいく 素敵なステージさ
Diving in with you—it's a wonderful stage
ここから これから
From here on out, from this moment on
アワー ブライト パレパレパレ
Our Bright Parade, parade, parade!
キャスト
Cast
セットリスト
Setlist
「RENEGADE」
“RENEGADE”
「アワータイムイエロー」
“Our Time Yellow”
「Genesis」
“Genesis”
「id:entity voices」
“id:entity voices”
「暁闇エクステシス」
“Gyōan Exstasis”
「Run Back 'Round」
“Run Back 'Round”
「Slap by Step」
“Slap by Step”
「Fortune Spinner」
“Fortune Spinner”
「Hyper Jumpin'」
“Hyper Jumpin'”
「Dramatic XViltration」
“Dramatic XViltration”
「青春アーカイブ」
“Seishun Archive”
「夢見る空へ」
“To the Dreaming Sky”
「We are GAMERS !!!!」
“We are GAMERS !!!!”
「キラメキライダー☆」
“Kirameki Rider”
「電脳ぴゅあお推し大宣言」
“Dennō Pure Oshi Daisengen”
「Shiny Smily Story」
“Shiny Smily Story”
「Prism Melody」
“Prism Melody”
「Show Them (Who You Are)」
“Show Them (Who You Are)”
「All for One!」
“All for One!”
「DEV_IS COUNTDOWN メドレー2025」
“DEV_IS COUNTDOWN Medley 2025”
「Our Bright Parade」
“Our Bright Parade”
この後は もう1本グランプリ！
Coming up next: Mo Ippon Grand Prix!
2026年もホロライブプロダクションをよろしくお願い致します！
We look forward to your continued support of hololive production in 2026!